nerdtests.com 2008-12-16

# NerdTests.com - Terms of Service and Privacy Policy

Updated: 04 Mar 2008, 10:50 CST

The following websites are part of the NerdTests.com network:  
    -DIGGTEST.COM  
    -EXTREMETESTS.COM  
    -GEEKTESTER.COM  
    -GEEKTESTS.COM  
    -HUMORBADGE.COM  
    -HUMOURBADGE.COM  
    -INSANETESTER.COM  
    -INSANITYTESTER.COM  
    -LOSERTESTER.COM  
    -LUCKYTESTER.COM  
    -MYTEST4U.COM  
    -MYTESTFORYOU.COM  
    -NARUTOTESTER.COM  
    -NERDHOTTIES.COM  
    -NERDHUNKS.COM  
    -NERDLOVING.COM  
    -NERDSPACES.COM  
    -NERDTESTER.COM  
    -NERDTESTS.COM  
    -NERDYPICS.COM  
    -QUIZCZAR.COM  
    -QUIZNEEDLE.COM  
    -RANDOTESTER.COM  
    -RUABLONDE.COM  
    -RUNESCAPETEST.COM  
    -RUSXC.COM  
    -SEXIESTNERD.COM  
    -SEXYBADGE.COM  
    -SEXYTESTER.COM  
    -STUPIDTESTER.COM  
    -TESTCZAR.COM  
    -TESTNEEDLE.COM  
    -WEIRDTESTER.COM  
    -ZOMBIETEST.COM 

The sites within the NerdTests.com network (herein referred simply as NerdTests.com) constantly strives to provide great service to you. 

NerdTests.com respects your right to privacy. The following describes how your information is handled. 

## NerdTests.com’s Commitment to Your Privacy 

NerdTests.com does not: collect personal information from you unless you provide it voluntarily; or provide or sell the names and physical addresses of customers [site users] to outside vendors. Users of the site who are under 13 years of age are not permitted to submit data that may or can be considered personal information.

NerdTests.com does: safeguard customers' information from unauthorized access; collect, maintain, and use customer information as necessary to provide the most helpful and targeted products and services to meet customers' needs; honor customers' requests to remove their names from the solicitation lists in a timely manner; and maintain confidentiality of customer information when undertaking additional projects. 

NerdTests.com always values your privacy. Your information will be protected as described unless the specific a web page states otherwise. 

## Information Gathered/Tracked 

**Statistics About Your Visit**

As you browse the NerdTests.com web site, NerdTests.com's web servers collect information about your visit, not about you personally. The following statistics may be monitored: the number of people whom visit this site; the IP address which you use to access this site; which pages people visit on this site; from which domains visitors come; which browsers people use to visit this site; and any additional information passed on to this site via your web browser. 

While NerdTests.com gathers this information, none of it is associated with you as an individual. These statistics help to improve this web site, to monitor its performance, and to make it easier for you and other visitors to use. Please be aware that the aforementioned information/data may be collected, and distributed or sold to third parties for their own statistical analysis.

**Organizational and Personal Information You Knowingly Provide**

You may be asked to give personal or organizational information in order to evaluate, purchase, or receive information about a product or service. This information varies depending on need, and only minimal, personal, information will be asked of you in order to fulfill the request. 

**Your IP Address and Host Name**

NerdTests.com's web site logs host names and IP addresses for system administration, security, and product distribution purposes. These logs are monitored and analyzed to secure the systems. 

## Cookies 

A cookie is a small, encrypted data string this server may write to your hard drive. This cookie is used to deliver web content specific to your interests and to control access to NerdTests.com premium content.

Additionally, third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on your website.

A cookie cannot be used to access or otherwise compromise the data on your hard drive. You can choose to change your browser settings to disable cookies if you wish. Please be aware that cookies may be required to complete certain functions at NerdTests.com.

## Links to Other Sites 

The NerdTests.com contains links to other Web sites. Please be aware this privacy policy does not apply to these sites. 

## Opt-out Policy 

NerdTests.com users are provided the opportunity to opt-out of receiving NerdTests.com communications. NerdTests.com users who wish to remove their information the database to avoid receiving future communications about services and product information can contact support@nerdtests.com. 

## Correcting/Update Policy 

If you would like to correct and/or update your information, please contact support@nerdtests.com. 

## Contractual Agreement between Site User and NerdTests.com

By using, surfing, viewing, or knowingly request information from NerdTests.com, you are implicitly agreeing to be lawfully held to this Privacy Policy.
